

Hussein Mohammadi Roozbahani

translator at Tarjomic

Bachelor of Petroleum engineering Petroleum University of Technology

Personal Information

Age: 23 Years

Gender: Male

Location: Tehran

Marital Status: Single

Military Service Status: Exempted

Contact Details

Phone: 02176273979

Mobile: 09215646501

Email:

h.mohammadi2079@yahoo.com Address: Tehran - Enghelab

LinkedIn: -

Last Update: 20 September 2022

Reference ID: **JV-96309420**

Iran Bandar abbas

Work Experience

translator May 2019 until now (3 years and 2 months)

Tarjomic Iran Tehran

translation of many contexts in the field of oil and petrochemicals, politics, Documents and contracts, movie and serial subtitles, geology as a silver translator, and social science as a golden translator.

intern at Iranian Off-shore Oil Company April 2022 until May 2022 (1 month)

Iranian Off-shore Oil Company (IOOC)

Intern at National Iranian Drilling Company April 2020 until May 2020 (1 month)

National Iranian Drilling Company (NIDC)

Intern at Trades and Technology Training complex June 2019 until July 2019 (1 month)

Trades and Technology Training complex Iran Ahvaz

Education

Bachelor - Petroleum engineering 2018 - 2023

Petroleum University of Technology GPA: 17.66

Training Courses

excel coursePUT university

Course Duration: 1 Month 2021

PVTI course PUT university

Course Duration: 1 Month 2020 (No Certificate)

Languages

English | Native

Software



Additional Skills

Translation Content Production

Honors & Awards

The third ranking in the whole university (3.65 GPA)

Projects & Academic experiences

Working on asphaltene precipitation reasons, probability, and ways to remove it (more precisely on

ely on

2022

Volunteer activities	
Organic chemistry teacher assistant	2019
advanced math teacher assistant	2020

Writing a review paper on carbon capture and storage (CCS) specially on CO2 purification and storage

About Me

solubility parameters of aspnaltene)

methods and its compatibility with Iranian oil reservoirs

Establishing Jahanara Oil and gas research institute

Sharp and extremely skillful in team work Having creative sprite Dedicated and responsible towards the duties keen on learning Oil software and machine learning in order to do projects using them Keen on working on smart well

2021

